explocity.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy - Explocity - Bangalore

## **Privacy Policy**

By “Explocity”, we mean Explocity Private Limited and [explocity.com](http://explocity.com/), its employees, managers, officers, shareholders, directors and to the extent that it is relevant to the context, its affiliates. By “website” or “site” we mean the contents of explocity.com (unless the context otherwise describes) as accessed at the time of usage and as inten[explocity.com](http://explocity.com/) by us. When you visit our site and any of the pages contained herein, you acknowledge that you have read the Terms of Use and Notice of Copyright and the Privacy Policy, and any other disclaimers. Further, you accept that you are bound by the terms and conditions spelled out by us, as may be modified from time to time. If you do not agree with any of our disclaimers below, please do not read the material on any of our pages

1.Explocity Pvt. Ltd values the privacy of information you choose to give us. We do not willfully use or disclose information about you, your visits to our website or any other information, like your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any third parties. The reason we collect any information from you is to be able to personalise the site for you. We will not use information about you without your permission and will provide the means for you to manage and control the information that you have provided. We do not disclose any personal information to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes that could be used to personally identify you, such as your password, credit card number and bank account number. However, information provided by you in or on content or pages co-branded with other parties may be shared with such parties without notice.

2.Credit card transaction information is protected by the industry standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and/or other methods. We use cookies to customise services. (Cookies contain data sent from our web server and stored on your hard disk. You may be required to accept cookies wherever you are prompted to login.)

3.The information you give us is also used to target advertisements to you according to what our advertisers want. This does not necessarily mean that they or anyone else has access to your personal information. For example: They will only receive general statistics, which are approximated to broad categories, such as people interested in culture or economics.

4.Please be careful when you give information about yourself on discussion groups or bulletin boards or in chat rooms because people may use that data to send you unsolicited messages.

5.The conditions under which we may disclose information is by process of law, to comply with legal or statutory, procedure, to enforce the Terms of Use, to protect the personal safety, the rights and property of Explocity, its registered members, its readers and the general public and to respond to claims by other parties if so reasonably required.

6\. We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting). Using the Ads Settings, visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.

7\. We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show ads on sites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website.

8\. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.

9\. We use data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics to understand our audience’s interests and browsing preferences to enhance their experience and our content.

**If you have any questions or need your doubts clarified, please write to us at[ corporate@explocity.com](http://bangalore.explocity.co.in/privacy-policy/corporate@explocity.com), we will get back to you as soon as we can.**
